=== MESH NAMES (first 50) ===
HOW TO ...  | Mat: Text
Incus.l  | Mat: Bone-1
Incus.r  | Mat: Bone-1
Malleus.l  | Mat: Bone-1
Malleus.r  | Mat: Bone-1
Stapes.l  | Mat: Bone-1
Stapes.r  | Mat: Bone-1
(Opponens digiti minimi muscle of foot).ol  | Mat: Origin-Adduction
Fibularis brevis muscle.el  | Mat: End-Extension hand-foot
Fibularis tertius muscle.el  | Mat: End-Extension hand-foot
Transverse head of adductor hallucis.e1l  | Mat: Origin-Adduction
Fifth metatarsal bone.l  | Mat: Bone
(Opponens digiti minimi muscle of foot).or  | Mat: Origin-Adduction
Fibularis brevis muscle.er  | Mat: End-Extension hand-foot
Fibularis tertius muscle.er  | Mat: End-Extension hand-foot
Plantar interossei muscles.o2l  | Mat: Origin-Adduction
Transverse head of adductor hallucis.e1r  | Mat: Origin-Adduction
Fifth metatarsal bone.r  | Mat: Bone
Lateral head of flexor hallucis brevis.o1l  | Mat: Origin-Flexion fingers
Long plantar ligament.o1l  | Mat: Origin-Ligament
Tibialis anterior muscle.e1l  | Mat: End-Flexion hand/foot
First metatarsal bone.l  | Mat: Bone
Lateral head of flexor hallucis brevis.o1r  | Mat: Origin-Flexion fingers
Long plantar ligament.o1r  | Mat: Origin-Ligament
Tibialis anterior muscle.e1r  | Mat: End-Flexion hand/foot
First metatarsal bone.r  | Mat: Bone
Long plantar ligament.o4l  | Mat: Origin-Ligament
Oblique head of adductor hallucis.o1l  | Mat: Origin-Ligament
Transverse head of adductor hallucis.e2l  | Mat: Origin-Adduction
Fourth metatarsal bone.l  | Mat: Bone
Long plantar ligament.o4r  | Mat: Origin-Ligament
Oblique head of adductor hallucis.o1r  | Mat: Origin-Ligament
Plantar interossei muscles.o1l  | Mat: Origin-Adduction
Transverse head of adductor hallucis.e2r  | Mat: Origin-Adduction
Fourth metatarsal bone.r  | Mat: Bone
Long plantar ligament.o2r  | Mat: Origin-Ligament
Second metatarsal bone.r  | Mat: Bone
Long plantar ligament.o2l  | Mat: Origin-Ligament
Second metatarsal bone.l  | Mat: Bone
Long plantar ligament.o3l  | Mat: Origin-Ligament
Transverse head of adductor hallucis.e3l  | Mat: Origin-Adduction
Third metatarsal bone.l  | Mat: Bone
Long plantar ligament.o3r  | Mat: Origin-Ligament
Plantar interossei muscles.ol  | Mat: Origin-Adduction
Transverse head of adductor hallucis.e3r  | Mat: Origin-Adduction
Third metatarsal bone.r  | Mat: Bone
Oblique head of adductor hallucis.er  | Mat: End-Adduction
Transverse head of adductor hallucis.or  | Mat: End-Adduction
Sesamoid bones of foot.r  | Mat: Bone-1
Extensor digitorum longus.e3l  | Mat: End-Extension fingers

Searching for Lungs or Visceral:
Circumflex artery of heart
Anterior basal segmental artery of left lung
Lateral basal segmental artery of left lung
Medial basal segmental artery of left lung
Posterior basal segmental artery of left lung
Superior segmental artery of left lung
Anterior segmental artery of left lung
Apical segmental artery of left lung
Inferior lingular artery of left lung
Posterior segmental artery of left lung
Superior lingular artery of left lung
Anterior basal segmental artery of right lung
Lateral basal segmental artery of right lung
Medial basal segmental artery of right lung
Posterior basal segmental artery of right lung
Superior segmental artery of right lung
Inferior lobar artery of right lung
Lateral segmental artery of right lung
Medial segmental artery of right lung
Middle lobar artery of right lung
Anterior segmental artery of right lung
Apical segmental artery of right lung
Posterior segmental artery of right lung
Superior lobar artery of right lung
Inferior basal vein of left lung
Superior basal vein of left lung
Superior vein of left lung
Anterior vein of left lung
Apicoposterior vein of left lung
Inferior lingular vein of left lung
Superior lingular vein of left lung
Lingular vein of left lung
Inferior basal vein of right lung
Superior basal vein of right lung
Superior vein of right lung
Anterior vein of right lung
Apical vein of right lung
Lateral vein of right lung
Medial vein of right lung
Posterior vein of right lung
Anterior lateral segment of liver (VI)
Anterior medial segment of liver (V)
Left anterior lateral segment of liver (III)
Left medial segment of liver (IV)
Left posterior lateral segment of liver (II)
Posterior lateral segment of liver (VII)
Posterior medial segment of liver (VIII)
Posterior segment of liver (I)
Liver
Inferior lobe of left lung
Superior lobe of left lung
Inferior lobe of right lung
Middle lobe of right lung
Superior lobe of right lung
(Anteromedial basal segmental bronchus of left lung)
Anterior basal segmental bronchus of left lung (BVIII)
Lateral basal segmental bronchus of left lung (BIX)
Medial basal segmental bronchus of left lung (BVII)
Posterior basal segmental bronchus of left lung (BX)
Superior segmental bronchus of left lung (BVI)
Anterior segmental bronchus of left lung (BIII)
Apicoposterior segmental bronchus of left lung (BI+BII)
Inferior lingular segmental bronchus of left lung (BV)
Superior lingular segmental bronchus of left lung (BIV)
Lateral segmental bronchus of right lung (BIV)
Medial segmental bronchus of right lung (BV)
Anterior basal segmental bronchus of right lung (BVIII)
Lateral basal segmental bronchus of right lung (BIX)
Medial basal segmental bronchus of right lung (BVII)
Posterior basal segmental bronchus of right lung (BX)
Superior segmental bronchus of right lung (BVI)
Anterior segmental bronchus of right lung (BIII)
Apical segmental bronchus of right lung (BI)
Posterior segmental bronchus of right lung (BII)
